How did you know that I have an apartment in Gangnam?
Why do you ask me that?
I don't think I said I knew it.
Somebody checked our family's background and I found who did it.
Who?
My son asked me a while ago if I have an apartment at Gangnam.
He doesn't know about the real estate or lands.
He didn't ask me so I didn't tell him about that.
She has a quite a temper. She isn't just any ordinary mother in a rich family.
He asked me about the apartment after he met you. You talked about this with him, right?
I don't know what you're talking about.
It doesn't make sense that a clever woman like you doesn't know about that.
I've met you several times.
You knew about it. I like how you're so honest and confident about yourself.
You shouldn't lie.
I think you're smarter than I am.
I thought you were just an ordinary mother in a rich family but you're like Sherlock Holmes.
I won't fall for it anymore. I'll lose if I fall for this.
I think a person should have common sense and duty to live one's life.
There are things you should do and shouldn't do.
While I was preparing the wedding with you,
I was very amazed when I saw an honest, energetic, and lively woman like you.
But now all your strong point have become your flaws in a blink of eye.
You have too much energy that you did things you weren't supposed to.
Please don't tell me you didn't.
If you make me think you're lying, I'll think of you as the worst woman.
I can use my brain to guess that at least.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Even if I said I did check your background...
I don't know if I should be treated like a human trash.
I would understand it if I were you.
You haven't screwed over by somebody, have you?
Somebody that you trusted hundred percent.
I have. I felt so empty after I got tricked by someone I trusted.
She said she's a rich and has her own buildings.
But she was nothing but window dressing. Have you meet a person like her?
When people say they're rich verbally, I don't trust them.
You're saying indirectly that you want to have rich in-laws.
Do you like money or not?
Wouldn't it be better if you have a lot of money?
If you say you don't like money, you're lying.
The hidden card is with me. How come she still looks so confident?
I will talk honestly with you.
You might think it's rude but since you crossed the line first, I'll do it, too.
If you have anything to say to me, say it.
When I was preparing the wedding with you, I was so tired.
That's what Jung Hoon said to me.
You were raised by rich families and got married to a great husband.
So, I don't think you care about other people.
I know you're educated but you don't have consider for others.
I do consider for others.
According to what you said to me so far, you got no consideration for others.
I said what I'm supposed to say. What should I have said then?
If somebody has consideration for others...
she would just try to understand them not blaming them.
Didn't you criticize about my family last time?
You made it sound like it was okay.
You were saying my family is disagreeable so you don't want to have me as in-laws.
You're misunderstanding now.
If you have common sense and dignity, you shouldn't ignore anybody. Aren't I right?
I didn't ignore you but I think if something doesn't suit for me, I should avoid it.
That was what I meant.
Even if we keep talking about this, our values and our ways won't change anyway, right?
So we should end the relationship between yours and my family.
We can't get along.
That's not important. Is it you and I that are going to live together?
I'm wasting time talking to you.
What you did was very brazen and shameless behavior.
I thought you would apologize to me at least.
You'd better convince her. If you don't, her feeling will get hurt.
I'm going to hurt her feelings. I know you have a big pride. Please convince her.
I don't have pride.
Why does my pride matter when it's about my child?
Do I need a pride to make money and living? My pride was gone a long time ago.
Episode 18
You are not going to touch my daughter.
- Is this ramen cooked now?
- I think it is.
I should make some side dishes.
If you don't have time, just order some. There are nice stores that sell side dishes.
I don't have time to find that place.
I will bring you some side dishes that I have now.
Thank you.
I just got proposed.
Really? From Gi Joong?
- I can't believe it.
- But, I'm not going to marry him.
Are you kidding me? Don't you remember you begged him to marry you.
I'm happy to get proposed by him though.
I think I'm just going to date Gi Joong now.
This is how you felt before.
You are telling me how happy you were to get proposed.
I was going to tell you what happened to me and Jong Hoon's mom but I shouldn't.
It's so hard to tell bad news to a happy person like you.
This is how you felt.
- Yeah. I was lonely when I was with you.
- I'm sorry.
You know what. Even after we worked out, I hesitated to come here.
There was a distance between you and me unlike before.
I was scared to tell you because you might say I'm an emotional trash.
I also feel like there was a wall between you and me unlike before.
It felt so weird.
I'm relieved that you feel the same as I do.
I wasn't the only weird one.
- Having a fight is a good thing I think.
- Why?
- I can understand you better now.
- Me too.
- If you don't want that ramen, let me...
- That's not going to happen.
I'm going to eat it all.
What are you doing here?
I'm meeting up with Hye Yoon during lunch time.
I guess she isn't here yet.
She will.
She's coming with Dong Bi.
- She comes here often.
- She should. She's my girlfriend.
- Didn't you date her before?
- It's different than before.
Yeah, you are changed compared to before.
- I don't think so.
- You are.
Hyung, I have to have a wedding so can I have the wedding here?
I think that's the best idea.
Why?
There's nowhere to do it. It costs money if I do it some other place but it's free here.
Who said it's free?
Fine, you can do it.
You really can make such a piteous look.
Holy cow.
How can she be so brazen like that?
She checked our background behind us.
I can't believe it.
I should do something about it.
- Honey, are you busy?
- Yeah, make it quick please.
I found out something ridiculous today.
I'd like to share it with you. If I tell you, you wouldn't want Jung Hoon to marry Hye Yoon.
Hurry home.
If he gets this text, he will change his mind.
- They're so late.
- I know. I should go back to the office.
It must be Hye Yoon.
Hye Yoon's mom checked our background.
Give up the apartment. You can't marry her.
That can't be Hye Yoon. They're coming now.
- Are you okay?
- It hurts.
Goodness.
You're so careless.
- I know.
- Why are you late?
The bus came late so we had to wait.
You should buy a car. You're so-called CEO.
Are you going to pay for the gas?
Why would I? You should pay for that.
Then, shut up.
Give us something to eat.
What is it that you're eating now?
That's Jung Hoon's. Make us new one.
- Didn't you eat?
- We had brunch.
We had a cup ramen. There was nothing to eat at her house.
That's not good.
Having a meal regularly is a basic need for a human. You don't have the basis.
See? You've changed. You're nagging.
Yeah. Nagging is full of love!
Don't make fun of me.
Gi Joong said we can have the wedding here.
- All we have to do is look for the house.
- Yeah.
How much do you pay for your apartment?
500,000 won for monthly rent.
That's expensive. You spend 500,000 won monthly just for the house.
You guys don't know anything. It's cheap because it's a studio.
A regular apartment will be more expensive than this.
But for a married couple, an apartment would be better than a studio.
Or a villa.
A lease would be better than a monthly rent.
Do you think I don't know that?
I still have money that I loaned from the bank.
I'll check if I can loan some money.
We don't have to live in Seoul. We can live in the suburbs of Seoul.
Because living in Seoul is expensive.
I hate this kind of conversation.
- What's wrong with our conversation?
- I know.
- When do you want to have the wedding.
- We can't do it on the arranged date, can we?
We can't. Let's do it a month after from now.
- Since you're busy, I'll get some information.
- Ok.
Let's go see your parents tonight.
We should go tell her we got back together.
Okay.
Everything is going so fast and smooth, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
Why are you here? I will bring food to the table.
It's tiring to be with them.
- Why?
- They only talk about the everyday living.
It's tiring. My head is mostly filled with those thoughts,
and to hear it again.
So?
I need healing.
Can't I?
Let's stay like this for a minute.
It hurts. Are you showing off your height now?
- I think it's been over a minute already.
- No, there is still a minute left.
Please stop Hye Yoon.
If you don't stop her, she will continue to get hurt. I will make it that way.
I've through something worse than this.
I am not someone who will just give up.
This is not about me but about Hye Yoon.
It's not the time for tears. All my hard work is about to be in vain.
Where did I say we are going?
To have fun.
Right, it' to have fun.
But you won't be just having fun with mom and dad alone. There will be another teacher to share the fun.
I understand.
- Are you ready?
- We are ready.
Let's go.
Where is this place?
It's court. It's family court.
What do you do in the family court?
Mom told you about divorce before.
- Living apart?
- Yeah.
This place helps in mom and dad's parting process.
You need help to part away?
What kind of help?
Tae Won, I will answer that question later at home.
You have keep the appointed time.
Do you want this?
Draw your family members here.
You know what family is right?
Mom, dad, aunt, grandmother, great aunt.
Do you live with your grandmother now?
She comes at night. In the morning she leaves to her store.
I see. Can you introduce your drawing of your family to me?
- You showed up so early (sarcasm).
- I had something to talk about with Dong Bi so I spent the night at her place last night.
I know everything. There is no need to hide.
About what?
I met Jung Hoon's mom yesterday and today too.
Do you know what she said to me?
I think she said the same thing to you too.
Don't worry about it. It's the two of us getting married.
Jung Hoon's mom thinks I acted rashly during the wedding preparation.
Because you asked to break up?
Yeah. I told Jung Hoon's parents that we broke up.
I understand that she would be angry.
Try to be understanding with me like how you are understanding towards her.
Do you know what she said to me?
I don't want to find out. What's the point? I will only get hurt more. Don't talk about it.
Fine, I don't want to talk about it either. It's too upsetting.
What did Jung Hoon say? What does he want to do?
We are firm now. We will get married even if it's just the two of us.
When?
4 weeks later.
Where?
The restaurant that aunt used for her wedding reception. We could use it for free.
Where will you live?
We need to look for a rental.
It's easy to say it now. But try living in a rental first,
you will see it's not as easy as you think.
Hye Jin said that the emotional indulgence I go through was possible because you fought with the world for my sake.
Before, I was jealous of Jung Hoon's mother.
Now, I don't envy her at all.
Before, I tried my hardest to not live like you do.
They say daughter's life takes after her mother's so I tried even harder.
But you know. Now, I want to live like you.
Why would you want to live like me? You have to live a better life.
I am Jung Hye Yoon, the daughter of a proud Lee Deul Ja.
I will get the things I want and keep them.
If I have to fight to get them, then I will fight and win.
But still, I don't think love conquers all. Jung Hoon's family situation is different now.
Jung Hoon's father must think differently from his wife.
Then it's all good. Even if she insists, she will be a ostracized.
I could hear the wheels in your brain rolling. What are you thinking about?
Right, why didn't I think of this before?
What?
Ostracizing her.
Which one is dad?
Here.
- Then what about mom?
This must be Tae Won. What are you doing here?
I am watching my mom and dad fight.
Hurry up What are you doing?
Okay, I'm coming.
How can I guy take longer to get ready to go out?
I forgot about my cell phone so I had to go back in.
Wait, let me use the bathroom.
You should have used it earlier.
It's not like we have an appointment. We are just going on a trip on our motorcycles. What's the rush?
That's true but I want to leave quickly.
I understand. Just wait a little.
I started riding motorcycle because of this sound.
Let's spend the night.
I am happy.
- Let's go!
- You have to take off your jacket.
- I will do it.
- You must be tired.
- I am alright.
- You knew mom and dad were fighting?
- Yes.
Since when?
From the beginning.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you'd cry.
You also know that I cry?
Yes.
You knew all along.
I am sorry.
I'm really sorry.
When you were drawing the family earlier, why did you draw your dad largest?
I drew you big too.
At the court earlier today,
you asked what kind of help is needed to part.
Yes.
I told you mom and dad parting is called a divorce.
But in order to get a divorce, you have to tell people you're getting divorced at the court where you went earlier today.
Why?
When people get married, they tell others too.
So marriage and divorce is not just between the two people
but you have to tell others.
Yes.
Mom and dad discussed everyday what's the best way to divorce.
Mom, dad, and Tae Won are family. Regardless of getting a divorce.
But mom, getting a divorce makes me sad.
I don't think it's a good thin. I just feel like crying.
What do you do in the family court?
I am saying this because it seems like you don't know what it is you want.
From what I could see, you want to continue living together with Hye Jin.
What are you.
- Are you going somewhere?
- I am going to drop by my house.
Did you have lunch? I packed lunch.
- I told you I am dropping by my house.
- Eat this first.
I told you to not come to the clinic.
You said you want to eat homemade food.
- Don't cook. You don't have to do such things.
- I will.
I don't want to eat something that doesn't taste good.
It will taste good.
You are not sensible. How can you pack fried rice? It's too dry.
It's simple. You don't need other side dishes to go along with it.
Good?
So so.
Make sure to remember how it tastes. It will get better tomorrow.
It must be good.
You are found out.
Why do you keep on asking to see me?
I cannot not see you forever. One thing you have to remember is that I was the first one to extend my hand to you.
- You like her that much?
- It's beyond like now.
Good for you for meeting someone like her. Let's say you're like that. Does she feel the same way about you?
She seemed a bit strange.
How?
She would argue back to me on every point. Usually others get nervous and unable to do so.
I first started liking her because she would not get nervous.
- When she had nothing to boast.
- She has no self-esteem or something?
You dumped her after dating her for 5 years. You were about to marry another girl and she dumped you. Then Dong Bi accepts you back?
Even when I was dating her, she would be a fool for me. I liked that.
She's nice. I liked that she's nice.
Her being a fool for me is not enough anymore. A meal would be nice.
What do you mean meal?
I have to marry her.
- Just date her only.
- 5 years is a long time for dating.
Why would I need to date her longer?
I have to live with her.
- Did she agree to it?
- No.
She's being absurd. Why wouldn't she want to marry you?
When someone like you is asking her for marriage.
Even if you're against it, I will marry her.
Your father would be against it. Why would I oppose? I won't oppose it.
I wanted to marry someone I loved too.
In the end, I ended up marrying your father,
but in my heart, I always plan to leave your father once I fall in love with someone.
Then do that.
I am used to living like this now. I know no other way.
Do as you wish. If you want to live with her, live with her. If you want to marry her, marry her.
I am still your mother. Would I want you to be unhappy?
- I get bored.
- I will be happy if you could be like this.
I don't know how you will be tomorrow.
Hye Yoon's mom ran a background check on us.
What?
She did a background check on our assets.
You're surprised too. How can she do such a thing?
- I think you're too much.
- About what?
The way how you act towards Hye Yoon's mother. Regardless of how much you dislike her, it's not good to condemn her like that.
Am I condemning her? I am not.
Then, how did you find out about that?
Did Hye Yoon's mother said she did that?
No, she insisted she didn't.
- You even asked her directly?
- Of course I did.
She needs to know we were duped.
How did you find out that she ran a background check on us?
When I went to the realtor, he asked me if I put our Gangnam Aparment for sale.
Some lady came saying she wanted to take a look at it.
Based on that, you think Hye Yoon's mother ran a background check?
When I met her earlier, she asked me if I own an apartment in Gangnam.
Please give me food.
- What?
- I need to eat.
Honey!
These days, I feel like your strengths are fading away.
What strengths?
Being like a girl, pure, not doubting others, and not calculating.
How can you think she ran a background check?
Why would she do that?
Because she wanted her daughter to marry into a rich family.
Are we rich? We are not. We decided to lay it all down and retire in the countryside.
Hye Yoon knows this already.
If her mother wanted her to marry into a rich family, after knowing this, she wouldn't have agreed to this marriage.
I am beginning to doubt if you could adjust to living in the countryside.
Even though I announced to Jung Hoon that I am on your side, I am hoping you'll stop.
I was surprised by how you treated Hye Yoon.
Regardless of how precious our son may be, how can you say such a thing to someone who's not even our daughter-in-law yet?
How will you face her once she becomes our daughter-in-law?
Such thing will never happen. Even if I may have to cut ties with Jung Hoon.
Why are you waiting outside? It's cold.
I wanted to see you as soon as possible.
I am so happy we're dating again.
My mom met your mother.
- I know.
- She already told you about it?
My mom is furious because your mother ran a background check.
Background check?
It doesn't matter if she did. I know her well.
To be honest, I guessed as much from before.
Why didn't you say anything?
I didn't think it's important.
Running background check doesn't cause any harm.
Your mother just wanted to check if her daughter chose to marry a really decent guy.
Thank you.
Let's go in now. Let's face our reality head on.
Yeah.
Hello, Mother-in-law.
Please accept my bow.
I guess you have something to say. Say it.
I am sorry for making you worry.
Hye Yoon and I will get married.
I met your mother today, she was threatening.
Parents from both families are important,
but we were too swayed and I don't want to make the same mistake.
It's good if you're not swayed
but how will you live?
Monthly rental?
- We will live according to our means
- Yes, mom.
I've thought hard about it, but if you don't have money to lease a place, come live under my roof.
What?
After Deul Rae married, I have a spare room. There is Hye Yoon's room too.
I have many spare rooms here. Why get a debt to find a plce?
You could live here for 2-3 years and move out after saving some money.
I need some time to think.
I told you this before too. If you think too long, you often make the wrong decision.
Yes.
You don't have feel burdened for living with me.
Because of my shop, I leave early in the morning and come home late at night.
And since you know me will, you already know that I don't have a tiring personality.
I could just go overboard at times.
- You'll have dinner here, right?
- Yes.
Wait.
Try to have your son taken away.
What can she do if I say I will live with him?
Your kid is not something you could abandon.
You will probably have a heartache.
Our kid already entered the elementary school. You're still pretty.
Slim and makes my heart flutter.
This is embarassing.
When I asked her for a peek she said never.
Yet she shows it to you.
What do you think of my mom asking you to live in this house?
It's too sudden so I don't really know.
If you're okay with it, I think it would be alright to live here.
With the money that we have, it will be difficult to get a lease (a lump sum money is given to the landlord at the move in and returned 100% at the time of moving out).
I will look into it favorably.
Of course living with my mom won't be easy and it will be stressful. However, it won't be forever.
You're right.
Come out and eat.
- Do you want more?
- After I finish this.
Your father must have liked to hear that you're dating Hye Yoon again.
Of course. My father likes her.
Alright.
We have many rooms. We have a spare bedroom too. You could spend the night here.
- No, mother.
- Don't feel pressured
and sleep in Deulrae's room. It would be a good idea to practice living together.
Mom!
I understand. I went overboard because it's nice to have a meal together.
- What are you doing?
- Can't you tell?
Give me a glass too.
It's so natural for you to order me around.
Have you forgotten? What's our current relationship?
How can I forget?
Drink slowly.
I will do as I wish.
Your mother isn't coming?
She's not coming. I better tell her not to come anymore.
It's hard on her to come back and forth and you show no signs of moving out.
If we get divorced, we should sell this house.
We should.
You decorated this house by yourself.
I was going to live the rest of my life here.
I was so through that the decorator got annoyed.
I liked this house.
You only slept here. What is there to like?
How about Tae Won?
He's sleeping.
Did you explain to him why he went to the court?
I am sorry.
Don't say you're sorry.
I am afraid my hatred towards you might lessen.
I am going to hate you. With all the energy that I have.
Why does Tae Won need to get hurt like this?
He should be innocent, immature, and pulling mischief at his age.
Why does he need to know what a divorce and court is?
Why does he have to go into his room and cry after seeing his parents fight?
It breaks my heart.
It's all your fault. It's your fault. You even have a woman.
You could live with her Why are you being like this?
What great wrong have I done while living with you?
You did well. You did no wrong.
But you make me a luxurious woman who relies on her mother at the court.
- Because I need to win.
- What's the point of beating me?
- I don't know.
- What?
If I really want to divorce you or not.
- What are you talking about?
- Like I said, I don't know.
I really don't understand you. Then what's with Yu Ri?
I know you're still meeting her.
You're the one who made the first move too
Crazy son of bi***.
Can't you hold onto me?
Go f*** yourself.
I will be back again, Mother.
Why are you coming out? It's cold.
- I will walk to to your car
- It's alright.
Don't you understand I want to be with you a little longer?
You have become a coquette while we've been apart.
I trained every night to show it to you when I saw you again.
Come here.
Why?
- I buried it here.
- What did you bury here?
Do you remember. The pot of plant we got at the wedding convention.
Yeah. You said you will take good care of it and bring it to our newly wed home.
It died. The root rotted.
I must have watered it too much and cared for it too much.
You can't water it too much and you can't have all your attention on this either.
I think love is the same way.
You said that before. I thought I have to do everything for the one that I love.
So I tried to do everything.
I realized that there are things you can't do even if you love someone, and there are things you need to stop caring about when you love someone too.
You've grown a lot while we were apart.
I think the reality changes when you love someone.
I think the reality could change.
I love you.
I was waiting for you.
- You got my text message?
- I did then I deleted it.
- Why?
- Because it doesn't matter.
You're as understanding as the Pacific Ocean. Try to be like that to me too.
Good night.
Why are you here?
You said there is nothing to eat at home.
Should I give you a hand?
You're helping by not helping.
I think you're right.
- By the way, what kind of soup are you making?
- Nutritious one.
Main ingredients are carrots, potatoes, and beef shank.
It's something I make when I am tired, it's a bit thin than typical soup.
Why are so good to me? It's weird. It's making me nervous.
I am not being good to you. I am doing what I want.
Why didn't you treat me this way before?
Because I was afraid you might like me too much.
You shouldn't like me too much. I couldn't be responsible for it.
- Can I keep watching?
- Just watch only. Don't touch the ingredients.
I won't touch it, instead...
I will touch you.
I have something to say.
Okay. Go on.
Hye Yoon and I will get married in 4 weeks. In Ki Joong's restaurant.
So you insist on creating trouble.
Regarding where we will live, we have many ideas. But as you know, we don't have much money so,
there aren't many options to choose from.
You could suffer a bit. You will realize how entitled your life was with your parents.
Mother-in-law suggested living in her house. So I am considering it.
What?
After Deul Rae married, only Mother-in-law and Hye Yoon are living there.
So they have a spare room. Also since Mother-in-law works, it won't be too inconvenient.
You are crazy over a girl and you lost your judgement.
How can you consider moving there?
I think it's better than taking out an unaffordable loan for housing.
Do as you wish. I won't talk out of it.
Move into that house or not. I don't care about your marriage anymore.
- You can't hate your mom
- I know.
Hye Yoon's family made a huge decision. You too.
It won't be easy to live with the in-laws.
It's the most realistic decision Hye Yoon and I can make now.
If that's what you guys think, you should do so.
You said you side with mom
You won't even come to the wedding?
If your mom doesn't attend, I can't attend your wedding by myself.
Are you crying again?
He's no longer my son. Really.
You need to lose to him.
It's not the matter of winning or losing. Jung Hoon's life depends on it.
I don't think there is anything wrong with Hye Yoon to be Jung Hoon's spouse.
You judge everyone generously.
You should lose to him. You have to lose to him eventually, so instead of later, just lose to him now.
The way how she thinks, I cannot beat her.
How did she come up with the idea to drag Jung Hoon into this.
- This won't do.
- What do you mean?
I have to become a hypocrite.
Why?
Rather than to see you becoming like this, it will be better for me to become a hypocrite.
- I am no longer neutral.
- Honey!
I will get ready for work.
He's the same. Exactly the same.
This tastes good.
- Come to the restaurant later.
- Why?
You will find out once you come.
Come here.
- We can't.
- What were you imagining?
Clumsy.
- What?
- Did you call me by chance?
I didn't.
- You don't care about me.
- Where are you now?
We went on an overnight motorcycle trip and just got back. I called you to tell you how fun it was—
Motorcycle? You ride a motorcycle?
We met through riding motorcycles. We shouldn't give it up.
These crazy ones. Why do you ride a motorcycle? What if you break a bone somewhere?
Would you like to eat lunch at home today?
I will make the braised pollack you like.
I can't make it for lunch. I have patients.
Sis. Do you want to have lunch together?
Should I wear the cardigan inside?
Come in.
What are you doing?
I have a blind date today. But I thought I look too clean-cut, you know I give the vibe of cha-do-nam, a cold urbane male.
I thought wearing a cardigan my soften my image a bit.
- I think it's better for you to skip the cardigan.
- Why?
You have a small frame, with a cardigan, you will look smaller and look cute.
- Cute?
- Yes.
Then I should wear it. I think girls like cute guys.
I want to be a cute guy.
So the mediation committee is scheduled for next week
Yes, it's next Tuesday.
Next Tuesday doesn't work for me, please reschedule it to next Wednesday.
I will.
So if we could reach a settlement in the mediation committee, the trial won't proceed anymore?
It's very unlikely that a settlement will be reached at the mediation committee.
Why? I would like to get this over with as soon as possible.
Because there is a huge gap between Mr. Nam Do Hyun and your requests.
Majority of the cases that settle in the mediation committee are for those with less than 30-50 million won ($30,000-50,000) in alimony.
This is very tiring. It takes a really long time.
Trials are always like that. You shouldn't get started on a trial, once it starts, it takes a long time.
The opposing party requested to trace my finances, is it in the process?
Yes. The account where lump sum is transferred to, who's account is that?
What will happen once it's revealed that its my money?
Those funds will be included under the division of assets as well.
Then it will become a bigger fight.
Then it would be pointless to transfer money into that account from this month.
You're right. Since they already know you're transferring money into that account, it's pointless.
- I understand.
- Then I will see you in court next week.
Yes, thank you for coming to meet me every time.
Here is the result for tracing his finances.
We found out the account holder of the account in which lump sum was transferred to.
Who is it?
It's Kang Min Ho.
- Really?
- Do you know him?
He's my uncle.
Why is your uncle helping Nam Do Hyun?
How come you're here alone? How about Aunt?
I heard you two went on a trip.
My wife went home. She said she's tired.
Wife? What wife? You don't even call her "wife"(in English) or "house person" (another term for wife).
Stop making fun of me and give me a laser treatment.
You could stop taking care of your looks now. Aunt, well, now it's sister-in-law, is older than you.
You don't have to try so hard. It's not like you're dating someone in their 20s.
You really have to look your best for your wife.
Wife, wife.
- I really can't stand it. Do you like it that much?
- I like it.
I like it too. You seem happy.
You still have a chance. Stop insisting on keeping your pride.
Go outside and wait. I will get it ready.
Why are you wearing sunglasses indoors?
I want to look at the world through a filter.
I wanted to talk to you because I was going through a hard time. But from the looks of it, I guess today is not the day.
You're having a hard time? Why?
- Are you happy to hear that I am having a hard time?
It's better to be going through a hard time together than me having a hard time alone.
I think being in a married relationship is quite funny.
Why? Your couple are so close together.
You know swans.
For a swan to look elegant in a lake,
how hard it has to move its feet in the water.
You don't know how hard I move my feet to be in a loving relationship.
So you're saying you and your husband's relationship is rocky too.
But you were faking it.
When I am being serious.
Don't overthink it. It only gives you a headache.
Take it easy. So what if you're not loved?
A woman that I know said this. She's a widow and she said there are advantages to having no husband.
I was shocked!
How can there be advantages for not having a husband?
Good for her. Since she doesn't have a husband.
I think there really are all sorts of people in this world.
So many different types. Ki Joong says he's getting married.
- With whom?
- She's a bit strange.
- They've dated for 5 years.
- Are you talking about Dong Bi? Mini Dong Bi?
How do you know her? She's friends with Jung Hoon.
- You are not against it?
- I am not against it.
I don't intend to.
I am sick and tired. It's his life.
You will change your mind later and give her a hard time.
I am upset because of Jung Hoon. He's creating a fuss insisting on marrying the girl with whom the engagement was previously broken off.
Husband, and kid. The ones who make you upset are the ones who makes me upset too.
What makes me angry is that my people, who are most important to me in this world, sides with those against me and criticizes me.
Eun Kyung, I like how you're today. I've lived such a life for dozens of year.
It gets better once you get used to it.
I can never let things pass this way.
Mom, you really want us to move in with you?
Move in with me, it's better that way. Do you think it doesn't cost much money for housing?
You got this idea from trying to ostracize my mother-in-law.
You're right. She will come to her senses once her son is taken away from her.
How can she be against her son marrying you?
On top of that, how she compares families, I can stand that even less.
Is it Joseon era now? Discriminating between the nobles and servants?
Her values are wrong.
It's not like that. She doesn't go that far.
What do you mean she doesn't go that far. She feigns innocence with those big eyes of hers.
She really knows how to handle people. When I met her I had my guards down and she knocked me down.
I really want to get married when the parents are against it.
Then you could try to convince her. I don't have much hope though.
Thank you for meeting me.
I think this is the first time you asked to meet.
In preparing for the wedding last time, I was the one who always called you.
I am sorry, Mother.
I shattered your dream of having a mother-in-law and daughter relationship different from any other.
My dream was shattered indeed.
I am slow to open my heart to people.
Also, I am bad at expressing myself so I couldn't live up to your expectation.
Forget it, what's the point of talking about the past?
It's not the past to me.
During the entire time preparing for the wedding, you saw me come short many times,
and saw that Jung Hoon was having a hard time stuck in the middle.
- That's why I thought I should let him go.
- Then you should have stuck to your decision till the end.
I told myself that many times but I couldn't help it.
You know it too. You loved your husband like that, so your married him.
My mother may be a bit brash, but she's someone you could get through.
Because she has excessive love for her kids to unexpected things take place,
but she's not a bad person.
Forget it. I think it's silly to have this type of conversation
I understand. I am going to stay out of your marriage.
- You don't have to be like this to me.
- Mother!
- Why did you ask me here?
- Follow me.
Here.
- Why are you giving this to me?
- It's yours.
I don't have money. I can't afford a car.
I am buying it for you.
- What are you doing?
- I think you're sick somewhere.
Why are you buying a car for me?
Did I ever say I will buy it? I will deduct it from your marketing budget.
Who are you do decide to deduct from that? I don't want it. I prefer money.
- Just take it.
- Why are you being like this? I can't get used to it.
Get used to it. Something like this will happen often in the future.
- Why?
- When I give you something, it makes me feel better.
If you're comfortable riding this car, I will feel even better.
Why are you like this to me?
Jerk, you're a jerk.
You're scaring me when you're like this all of a sudden.
Since you're suddenly like this, I feel like you're being extra nice before discarding me.
I asked you to marry me, how did you take me for?
- How about the parents?
- You don't need to worry about it, I will take care of it.
- How?
- The only thing you need to decide
is whether to marry me or not. Do you not want to marry me?
I like it.
- You're here.
- Yes, where is my wife?
She said she will come home late. I will get the dinner ready.
Yes. Alright.
This room probably needs new wallpapers.
Is this room too small for the couple?
Should I make Hye Yoon's room the newlywed's room?
- What are you doing, mom?
- Where have you been?
- I met mother(-in-law).
- What did she say?
She said she will stay out of our wedding.
Tell her to do whatever she wants. It's better if she stays out of it.
She has a privileged life.
Is this room better or your room better for the newlywed's room?
- We haven't decided yet.
- What is there to decide?
Why waste money when you have this house?
Do you want to live with us?
When I want to think about that woman, I want to rub it into her by living with her son.
Is she that great?
Where have you been? You didn't answer my calls.
What are you doing? I am going to sleep in Jung Hoon's room.
You could sleep with your son. He's not my son anymore.
Even if we fight, let's stay in the same room and fight.
I don't want to stay in the same room with the hypocrite.
I experienced my whole life falling apart today.
I have given it my all for this family.
I am treated worse than Hye Yoon.
Get out. Spend the night in your father's room.
Mom.
I really feel like my whole life has been insulted.
In order to keep this family well, I have tried so hard.
Did I ever say I don't know that? That's a separate issue from my wedding.
What is that a separate issue? How many times do I have to tell you?
Hye Yoon's mom running a background check for her kid is not a big deal,
yet you think my acting like this seems selfish to you, right?
- Mom.
- Go live with her.
Live with that woman and Hye Yoon. I won't talk you out of it.
- Dad.
- Do you want to sleep with dad?
Mom, what do I do?
Do as you wish.
Tae Won, why do you ask mom that?
If you get divorced, I will live with mom and dad comes to play with me, isn't it?
It's not. You could live with me too.
Do you not want to live with me?
Then what about mom?
Mom will come visit you. You and I will live together, the two of us.
Like how we have been doing, can mom, dad, and me live together? You don't have to move out.
- We see each other often.
- Right.
I haven't pressed the button it. Can you press the button please? 3rd floor.
That's where the mediation office we are going to is located.
Please sit.
Plaintiff Nam Do Hyun. Do you still want to divorce?
Yes.
Defendant, Jung Hye Jin. Are you divorcing?
Defendant Jung Hye Jin, please step out. I will ask you back in after questioning the plaintiff.
Why are they asking me to step out?
Since the plaintiff and the defendant's assertions are very different,
they want to come to a conclusion after hearing from each party.
Plaintiff Nam Do Hyun, what's the reason for this divorce?
If possible, just don't go through with the divorce.
Pardon.
Getting a divorce is nothing great.
Think about the kid and live with her.
You even cheated.
Then you are the spouse with the fault, so you will be at a disadvantage.
Do you really want to divorce?
I don't want to get a divorce.
Convince Mrs. Jung Hye Jin and ask her to drop the suit.
Even if you don't want to get divorced now, since we're already at this junction, we can't stop it.
Then why do you keep asking? It's not something that can be solved if I stop.
I am giving you a chance to persuade the other party.
Forget it. I just wanted to find out what will happen if I said I don't want to proceed with the divorce now.
Then how much will you give her to get a divorce?
You know that since you're the spouse who did wrong, you're at a disadvantage, right?
I am not the only one who did wrong. During the entire marriage, she spent my money endlessly.
Luxury handbags, clothes. She changed the furniture every season.
She's the wife of a successful doctor in Gangnam,
how can you call that an extravagant lifestyle?
Once she spends all the money there is to spend in Korea, that will be equivalent to the Civil Code Article 840 Section 1 crime of spousal corruption.
I said I didn't cheat.
That's just hiding your head in the sand.
All the evidence is here.
I offered $100,000 in alimony
for division of assets, I could give her about $500,000 once all the assets have been sold and divided afterwards.
How about the child support?
I am going to raise him, why should I pay the child support?
She should be paying me.
I cannot give up the custody. I was given $10,000 per month for living expense.
I need to be paid $5,000 per month for child support following the previous living standard.
For division of assets, the other party offered $500,000
Ridiculous. That's less than 1/2 of our current house.
You're requesting $4 million for division of assets and $100,000 for alimony.
From the other party's assets known to us so far, he doesn't have that much assets.
It will be hard to mediate. The difference between party's amount offered is too big
and requested documents have not been submitted in full.
I will have to conclude as mediation not reached.
Please solve the misunderstanding with the other party.